Hello sir quick question for you we go all
over the country just asking people a few quick
questions on their advice to the younger
generation of kids starting out in the real
world today we thought you had a beautiful house
wanted to know if we could ask you a
few quick questions for the channel hey he opened
that up so you guys see the lamborghini he's got
the aston martin out got a whole bunch of cars we
gotta figure out what this guy did to be able to
put himself here excuse me sir is this your house
it is what do you do for a living man
los angeles is the number six city in the
entire world with the most millionaires today we're going
to be going all over los angeles
bel-air beverly hills and calabasas asking multi-million dollar
homeowners how they became successful and how you
can start your path to becoming wealthy in 2023
right now in the hidden hills of bel-air
one of the most expensive and wealthy neighborhoods
in the entire country and with that being
said let's get this video on the way
so
you
, so growing up i always used to hear
about how beverly hills had all these multi-million dollar
mansions where all your favorite rappers and movie
stars live well today we're going to be
going up to these homes for ourselves i want to
run into some of the craziest people in the entire
city to figure out what they did to put
themselves in these multi-million dollar houses i got the
bentley parked out front we're going to go
up to the door ask this multi-million dollar homeowner
how they were able to put themselves here
let's see what they have to say excuse me
Ma'am, quick question for you.
My brother and I, we go all over the country.
We're based in Austin, Texas.
We grew a channel to over 2 million followers
where we go all over the country
just asking beautiful homeowners a few questions
on their advice to the younger generation.
Wanted to know if we could ask you
just a few quick questions for the channel.
I'd love to, come on in.
Is that cool?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
I love you entrepreneurs.
Thank you.
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
22 years.
What industry did you pursue a career in?
Well, I was a former model,
but when that was over,
I went into renovating homes
and then building homes.
So you've been an entrepreneur for a long time now.
Over that period of time,
what's the greatest lesson about entrepreneurship
that you've learned that you pass on to someone
who's about to start their first business in 2023?
Well, one of the things that
I love to teach my son
is take a risk.
Take a risk.
You know, I had nothing
and I just believe that if you believe in yourself
and you believe in what you do,
then the chances are you will be a success.
What would you say has
been the most amount of money
that you've ever generated in a single year?
Cover your ears, cover your ears, cover your ears.
Well,
my last property I made,
I made three and a
half million on my last property.
That's incredible.
Look at the face, look at the face.
Now he definitely wants to
come into my business, don't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
But I'll make more on this one.
How are you able to
scale from six to seven figures
and then just from beyond that?
Yes.
So I was very lucky that
I was able to reinvest my profit
over and over and over.
And what that did was that allowed me
to get larger and larger and larger.
And then the other thing that you can do
is do a 1031 exchange.
And what that does, it allows
you to push out your taxes
because you're rolling your profit into your next build.
So that just allows you to
go bigger and bigger and bigger.
Eventually you're going to say,
OK, I've got to stop now.
Yeah.
But yes, it's that's a very handy tool as well.
And my final question for you,
you know, you've got a beautiful,
one of the most beautiful houses I've been in.
This is a multimillion dollar house.
What would you say is the best advice
that you pass on to the younger generation?
Well, I, you know, I'm a
great believer in hard work pays off.
And so he asked me, I
said, well, I'm a hard worker.
He actually has my gene.
He is.
He is me.
He's my mini me.
So hard work.
Stay focused.
I tell him this every day, don't I?
Know your goal.
Focus on the goal and
don't stop until you get there.
I love it.
Phenomenal advice.
Great interview.
Thank you so much for your time.
I really appreciate that.
Gio, thanks for joining us, man.
All right, you guys, that
was an absolutely insane experience.
She invited us into her house, was a former model
and is now a real estate developer in Los Angeles.
One of the most competitive industries to be in.
And she is a multimillionaire.
She's an absolute mogul.
Had her son out to teach him.
Financial lessons.
But you can tell he's going
to be very successful one day.
Los Angeles is absolutely insane, man.
Keep this going.
Hello, sir.
Yeah.
Question for you.
Thought you had a beautiful house.
Want to know if we could
ask you just a few quick questions.
Uh, no, I would like to opt out.
What's that?
I would like to opt out.
No worries, sir.
Have a good day.
Even though we started the day
off with a crazy first interview,
over the next six hours, we had
no idea what was coming our way.
Hi, my name is James Dumlin.
Wanted to know if we could ask
you or someone a few quick questions
on your advice to the younger generation.
You know, I'm kind of busy right now.
Um, why don't you just move on?
I just don't really have time right now.
No worries.
Damn it, bro.
Hi, ma'am.
Question for you.
I started a channel that I
grew to over two million followers.
How you doing, sir?
Just asking beautiful homeowners a few quick questions
on their advice to the younger generation.
Yeah, um, homeowner likes to be very private.
Okay.
I think I've seen your channel, by the way.
Yeah, thank you, bro.
Yeah.
No worries, man.
Sorry about that.
No worries.
Have a good one, bro.
Although we faced rejection after rejection for hours,
right before we decided to
call it a day, this happened.
I go all over the country.
I'm based in Austin, Texas.
Just asking people a few quick questions on their advice
to the younger generation.
Could I ask you just
a few quick questions up here?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you, sir.
Appreciate that.
We'll just come.
Awesome.
So what industry did you
decide to pursue a career in?
Software engineering, and then I turned it into marketing.
Are you a business owner now?
Yes.
And how long have you been a business owner for?
I've been running my agency for nine years.
You've had longevity as an
entrepreneur for nearly 10 years now.
90% of businesses don't make it.
So what would you say is the
most common mistake that business owners make
that prevents them from having longevity?
Okay, so a couple of things.
I've run a startup and failed at building a startup.
And the company wasn't a huge success.
It ended up being acquired, but ultimately,
it wasn't the multi-billion dollar
company I expected it to be.
And in those days, it was
like, don't get down on yourself.
Don't start second guessing yourself
and just keep working at it.
Every single day is a new day
and you can do something new with that.
You can always keep trying to move forward.
I think that's the biggest thing.
Keep moving forward with everything that you're doing.
If there's a mistake that you made or
you don't see sales going the right way,
just keep trying and keep pushing at it
and try to figure out what you can do
to get to that next level.
But also, make decisions.
I think the biggest thing that's
helped me in my career has been
I'm very quick to make a decision.
I feel like I can make
a decision in a split second.
And I don't overthink things and
don't worry about too many things.
I just jump right in.
Early on, I always just was like, I hustled.
I figured out how to get stuff done.
And I never took any shortcuts is what I'll say.
You've got great advice.
Thank you so much for your time, sir.
I appreciate you.
And one last final thing.
Any advice to someone who wants
to own a Porsche one day?
This is a multi-hundred thousand dollar.
This is a lot of people's dream car.
Any advice?
It's my dream car.
When I was a kid, I actually used to
always go to the auto show with my dad.
And I'd get the 911 posters or pamphlets or whatever.
And I'd hang them up in my room.
And it's been my dream car.
Just work hard, invest well, save, and go for it.
All right, you guys.
My man was driving down the street in the Porsche.
And we yelled at him from outside of the car.
Excuse me, sir.
We let him know about
the channel and what we do.
Went up to him and asked him some questions.
It turned out he was
a beast entrepreneur, a marketing multimillionaire.
Started out as a software engineer.
Transitioned.
Now he's a business mogul.
So caught him in the Porsche.
He gave some incredible advice.
Shout out to that man right there.
Let's get the next one.
All right, you guys.
We're out in Calabasas in Los Angeles, California.
This is one of the
wealthiest parts in the entire city.
And as I said earlier, man, Los Angeles.
This is the number six city in
the entire world with the most millionaires.
We're here at our next
multimillion dollar house out in Calabasas.
We're going to go to it.
See if we can get some game from the owner.
Figure out how they were able to
put themselves in a house like this.
Hello, sir.
Quick question for you.
My two friends and I, we
started a channel in Austin, Texas.
It grew to over two million followers.
We go all over the country just asking people
a few quick questions on their advice to the
younger generation of kids starting
out in the real world today.
We thought you had a beautiful house.
Wanted to know if we could ask
you a few quick questions for the channel.
That's amazing.
Is it cool if we come in?
Hey, you open that up.
So.
You guys see the Lamborghinis got the Aston Martin out.
Got a whole bunch of cars.
We got to figure out what this guy
did to be able to put himself here.
How you doing, sir?
Hey, what's up?
Man, you got a beautiful house here.
Thank you.
Are you are you from Los Angeles originally?
I was born in Columbia.
I came here when I was six years old.
How did you end up in Los Angeles?
So my parents, they had this dream to come to the US and unfortunately became a nightmare because two weeks
after we came to the US, our home got raided by law enforcement and both my parents ended up in jail.
How were you able to bounce back from that?
Kind of like going through that at an early age?
Like what was the turning point?
The turning point that really allowed you
to kind of build all of this?
Well, at ten years old, when they really put my dad away for a long time, I made him a promise that I'd take care of
the house and I became the head of household at 15 years old and I got a chance to start working early and then I started hustling.
You got a super nice spot here.
It's a multimillion dollar home.
Could we check out the spot a little bit?
Let's check it out.
Awesome.
What industry did you decide to pursue?
Home security.
I've had that now for 25 years and I just started a solar company a year
and a half ago, which just happens to be the 20th fastest growing company in Inc.
5000 Magazine.
How old were you when you started your first business?
I was 21 years old.
21. And how old are you now?
I'm 46.
What's the most amount of money that your
business has ever generated in a single year?
It'll be this year. We'll do 200 million.
Scaling is one of the hardest
thing to do as a business owner.
A lot of people don't have that great idea,
but they don't know how to scale and grow it.
So how have you been able
to scale to a nine figure business?
It has to come back to influence.
Right? Because to bring in good
people, they have to believe in you.
You know, your dream has got to be so
big that everybody's dream can fit inside of it.
Because again, good people, they have a lot of
options, but you got to take the first step.
Faith is really taking action
before you have what you need.
I remember as soon as I started the home security company, I bought the minivan before I actually had the people because
we used to go in minivans and I used to fill all of them up and we used to go door to door.
I didn't have a team yet, but I
bought the minivan knowing that the people were coming.
When you put money behind something, that's when you know.
You're committed.
I call it a necessity level and necessity levels, this sudden willingness
that untaps this tremendous amount of ability that you didn't know you had.
That's why I've always been great at putting
myself in pressure situations that increase my urgency level.
I believe low stress is low performance.
But when you put yourself in these uncomfortable situations,
that's when that greatness that lies within comes out.
What's been your secret to sales?
You know, you sold hundreds of millions of
dollars in revenue at your company throughout your career.
But how have you really.
Been able to land big deals
with massive clients over all these years?
I've always gone out of my way to validate
the business that I'm in to give me confidence.
So like when I started selling home security going door
to door, I would look up articles of home invasions.
I would look up fire accidents that were happening.
And what that did is it
filled me up with belief, with confidence.
And that's important because the more certain
person will always influence the less certain person.
People don't have to believe what you're saying.
They have to believe that.
You believe what you're saying
because everything's a transfer of belief.
You've generated hundreds of millions of
dollars in revenue throughout your career.
What has been the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
One of the great things that I did when I first started was I
would split my check three ways and I would live on a third of it.
One would go towards IRS and savings.
And then the other one would go towards
a reserve account that no one could touch.
You could call me and ask me for money.
To me, that reserve account did not exist.
And that reserve account has always helped me through
tough times because in life, life and pain are inseparable.
And you're going to have to go through
some tough times because I liked nice things.
But being able to cut it three ways
allowed me not to live outside my means.
That said, I was huge on having nice things.
It's what made me want to work hard.
I wanted to stand out.
I wanted to be rare.
You know, at 21 years old, I wanted to be
the first 21-year-old in my city driving a Mercedes convertible.
I didn't want to do it when I was
28 because by then everybody had a Mercedes, right?
So just little ways that I would compete against myself.
You don't come from a rich family.
A rich family can come from you.
And I made the decision in my family that I was
going to be the one person that changed my family tree forever.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video.
Be sure to leave a like and
subscribe for some amazing content coming soon.
And everybody click right here to watch us going all around
Miami, Florida, asking multimillionaires how you can become successful in today's world.